<resources>
  <string name="app_name">9th Age Quick Setup</string>
  <string name="bottom_navigation_quick_game_setup">Quick game setup</string>
  <string name="bottom_navigation_battle_outcome">Battle outcome</string>
  <string name="options_include_aleternative_maps">Alternative maps</string>
  <string name="generateNewConfiguration">Roll for new set</string>
  <string name="enlarge">Enlarge</string>
  <string name="details">Details</string>
  <string name="deployment">Deployment</string>
  <string name="ok">OK</string>
  <string name="preview_list">Preview list</string>
  <string name="points">%d\u200Apts</string>
  <string name="conflict_side_choose_hint">Army owner:</string>
  <string name="conflict_side_me">This is my army</string>
  <string name="conflict_side_opponent">This is my opponent\'s army</string>
  <string name="deployment_01">Frontline Clash</string>
  <string name="deployment_01_description">Deployment Zones are more than 12′′ away from the Central Line, towards your Long Table Edge, and more than 6′′ from the Short Table Edges.</string>
  <string name="deployment_02">Bottleneck</string>
  <string name="deployment_02_description">Player A’s Deployment Zone is more than 9′′ away from the Central Line, towards your Long Table Edge, and more than 12′′ from the Short Table Edges. Player B’s Deployment Zone is more than 15′′ away from the Central Line. The player who chooses their Deployment Zone also chooses if they are player A or player B.</string>
  <string name="deployment_03">Spearhead</string>
  <string name="deployment_03_description">Deployment Zones are more than 15′′ away from the Central Line. The table is divided along the long Table Edge into three equal areas (“west”, “centre”, “east”). The player who chooses their Deployment Zone also chooses one of these thirds to be their “Spearhead Area”. The other player then chooses one of the remaining two thirds as their own Spearhead Area. Units Deployed fully within their Spearhead Area gain Vanguard (3′′).</string>
  <string name="deployment_04"> Mutual Encroachment</string>
  <string name="deployment_04_description">Deployment Zones are more than 12′′ away from the Cen- tral Line, towards your Long Table Edge, and more than 6′′ from the Short Table Edges. When Deploying, each player may Deploy up to two of their Scoring Units from the “Core” Army Category fully on their own half of the Battlefield and fully within any Field, Forest, Ruins (by “fully”, we mean that no part of their Unit Boundary can be outside the Terrain Feature or on the opponent’s half of the Battlefield). Units Deployed in this way cannot declare a Charge, per- form Advance Move or perform a March Move in the first Player Turn of the first Game Turn.</string>
  <string name="deployment_05">Refused Flank</string>
  <string name="deployment_05_description">Deployment Zones are more than 9′′ away from the Central Line (see figure), which is the line drawn from one corner of the Battlefield to the opposite corner. The player who chooses their Deployment Zone also chooses which corners to use for the Central Line.</string>
  <string name="deployment_06">Cornerstone</string>
  <string name="deployment_06_description">Deployment Zones are more than 12′′ away from the Central Line, towards your Long Table Edge, and more than 6′′ from the Short Table Edges. The first unit each player Deploys must be their most expensive Rank-and-File unit (as determined by their Army List). This unit must be Deployed within 6′′ of the Central Line that is parallel to the Short Table Edges (the dashed red line in the figure). When Deployment is finished, each player must have Deployed an as equal number of units as possible on each side of the first Deployed unit (which side a unit is Deployed on is defined by which Short Table Edge the unit’s Centre is closer to, compared to the first Deployed unit). Ignore Attachable Models that start the game joined to a unit for this purpose.</string>
  <string name="deployment_preview">Deployment Preview</string>

  <string name="primaryobjective">Primary Objective</string>
  <string name="primaryobjective_01">Spoils of War</string>
  <string name="primaryobjective_01_description_short">Setup during Pre-game Selections: None.</string>
  <string name="primaryobjective_01_description">Rules: when an enemy Scoring Unit is Destroyed in Combat, the opposing player puts one Spoils Token on one of their Scoring Units (if there are any), that was just Engaged with the unit Destroyed in Combat. A unit loses all its Spoils Tokens if all its Rank-and-File models are removed as a casualty, or it becomes Shaken.
\n\nWinning conditions: at the end of the game, the player with the most Spoils Tokens on their units wins this Primary Objective.</string>
  <string name="primaryobjective_02">Breakthrough</string>
  <string name="primaryobjective_02_description_short">Setup during Pre-game Selections: Mark Deployment Zones.</string>
  <string name="primaryobjective_02_description">Rules: None.
    \n\nWinning conditions: At the end of the game, each player adds together the number of Scoring Units in their opponent’s Deployment Zone and the number of enemy units that were Scoring at the start of the game that were Destroyed in Combat. The player with the highest total wins the Primary Objective.</string>
  <string name="primaryobjective_03">Secure Target</string>
  <string name="primaryobjective_03_description_short">Setup during Pre-game Selections: place two markers with their centres on the Central Line, one on each side of the centre of the Battlefield, as close as possible to a sixth of the length of the long Table Edge away from the Short Table Edges, and more than 1′′ away from Impassable Terrain. Note: on a standard 72′′ Battlefield, the markers are 12′′ away from the Short Table Edges and 48′′ away from each other.</string>
  <string name="primaryobjective_03_description">Rules: a marker is “controlled” if a player has at least one Scoring Unit within 6′′ of the centre of the marker, and the other player does not.
    \n\nWinning conditions: at the end of Game Turns 3 to 6, an Objective Counter is awarded to a player who controls at least one marker. The player with the most Objective Counters at the end of the game wins this Primary Objective.</string>
  <string name="primaryobjective_04">Forage and Plunder</string>
  <string name="primaryobjective_04_description_short">Setup during Pre-game Selections: mark a total of three different Terrain Features that are not Walls or Impassible Terrain: first, mark the Terrain Feature closest to the centre of the Battlefield. Then, each player marks one Terrain Feature that is fully outside of their Deployment Zone.</string>
  <string name="primaryobjective_04_description">Rules: you automatically “plunder” a marked Terrain Feature, that you have not already plundered, when a friendly Scoring Units starts any of its Player Turns 3 to 6 in contact with it. Both players can plunder all marked Terrain Features once, even if the other player has already done so.
    \n\nWinning conditions: at the end of the game, a player who has plundered more marked Terrain Features than the other player wins the Primary Objective.</string>
  <string name="primaryobjective_05">Hold the Centre</string>
  <string name="primaryobjective_05_description_short">Setup during Pre-game Selections: mark the centre of the Battlefield.</string>
  <string name="primaryobjective_05_description">Rules: the Battlefield is “controlled” by the player who has the most Scoring Units within 9′′ of the centre of the Battlefield (if both players have an equal number of Scoring Units, no one controls it).
    \n\nWinning conditions: at the end of Game Turns 3 to 6, an Objective Counter is awarded to a player who controls the Battlefield. The player with the most Objective Counters at the end of the game wins this Primary Objective.</string>
  <string name="primaryobjective_06">Hidden Agendas</string>
  <string name="primaryobjective_06_description_short">Setup during Pre-game Selections: None.</string>
  <string name="primaryobjective_06_description">Rules: each player randomly picks one additional Secondary Objective, following the rules for Random Selection of Secondary Objectives.
    \n\nWinning conditions: for each completed Secondary Objective, a player scores 2 Battle Points, and the opponent loses 2 Battle Points. This replaces the normal scoring and losing of Battle Points for both Primary and Secondary Objectives.</string>

  <string name="primaryobjective_05_legacy">Breaking flags</string>
  <string name="primaryobjective_05_description_short_legacy">Valuable targets must be annihilated.</string>
  <string name="primaryobjective_05_description_legacy">After Spell Selection (at the end of step 7 of the PreGame Sequence), mark all Scoring Units on both players’ Army Lists. If either player has fewer than 3 marked units, their opponent must mark enough units from this player’s Army List so that there are exactly 3 marked units in the army, starting with the player who chose their Deployment Zone.
    \n\nThe player who has the lowest number of their marked units removed as casualties at the end of the game wins this Secondary Objective.</string>
  <string name="primaryobjective_06_legacy">Secure Target</string>
  <string name="primaryobjective_06_description_short_legacy">Critical resources must not fall into enemy hands.</string>
  <string name="primaryobjective_06_description_legacy">Immediately after determining Deployment Zones, both players place one marker on the Battlefield, starting with the player who chose their Deployment Zone. Each player must place the marker with its centre on a point that is more than 12″ away from their Deployment Zone and at least a third of the long Board Edge length (24″ on a standard board) from the point marked by the other marker.
    \n\nAt the end of the game, the player controlling the most markers wins this Secondary Objective. A marker is controlled by the player with the most Scoring Units within 6″ of the centre of the marker. If a unit is within 6″ of the centres of both markers, it only counts as within 6″ of the centre of the marker which is closest to its Centre (randomise if both markers’ centres are equally close).</string>

  <string name="mysecondaryobjective">My Secondary Objective</string>
  <string name="opponentsecondaryobjective">Opponents Secondary Objective</string>

  <string name="secondaryobjective_01">Capture the Flag</string>
  <string name="secondaryobjective_01_description_short">Setup during Pre-game Selections: None.</string>
  <string name="secondaryobjective_01_description">Rules: None.
\n\nWinning conditions: you complete this Secondary Objective if, at the end of the game, you have more Standard Bearers and Battle Standard Bearers on the Battlefield than the opponent has.</string>

  <string name="secondaryobjective_02">Commit to Battle</string>
  <string name="secondaryobjective_02_description_short">Setup during Pre-game Selections: None.</string>
  <string name="secondaryobjective_02_description">Rules: None.
\n\nWinning conditions: you complete this Secondary Objective if, at the end of the game, you have more Scoring Units in your opponent’s Deployment Zone than the opponent has (in their own Deployment Zone).</string>

  <string name="secondaryobjective_03">Demonstrate Superiority</string>
  <string name="secondaryobjective_03_description_short">Setup during Pre-game Selections: the opponent marks the two most expensive Scoring Units on their Army List. If there is only one Scoring Unit, also mark the most expensive Rank-and-File Unit. If there are no Scoring Units, mark the two most expensive Rank-and-File Units instead. In any case of tie, randomize.</string>
  <string name="secondaryobjective_03_description">Rules: None.
\n\nWinning conditions: you complete this Secondary Objective if, at the end of the game, at least one of the marked units is removed as a casualty, Decimated, Shaken, or in contact with its own Deployment Zone.</string>

  <string name="secondaryobjective_04">Enslave and Ransom</string>
  <string name="secondaryobjective_04_description_short">Setup during Pre-game Selections: None.</string>
  <string name="secondaryobjective_04_description">Rules: you gain a “Prisoners” Counter every time an enemy unit is Destroyed in Combat. If the unit is removed as a casualty in step 5 of the Round of Combat Sequence (“Breaking and Pursuing”), you gain an additional Prisoners Counter. This includes failing a Break Test and being caught by a Pursuing unit, but also units being removed as casualties due to initiating a Flee Move while Decimated, Supernal units failing a Break Test, or Unstable units losing a Combat and being wiped due to the resulting HP losses, but does not include units being removed as casualties as a direct result of Melee Attacks. For this purpose, ignore Attachable Models joined to Rank-and-File Units.
\n\nWinning conditions: you complete this Secondary Objective if, at the end of the game, you have at least four Prisoners Counters.</string>

  <string name="secondaryobjective_05">Forbid Trespass</string>
  <string name="secondaryobjective_05_description_short">Setup during Pre-game Selections: mark a Terrain Feature on the Battlefield that is fully outside your Deployment Zone, and that is not a Wall nor Impassable Terrain.</string>
  <string name="secondaryobjective_05_description">Rules: the marked Terrain Feature is “plundered” when an enemy Scoring Unit starts any of its Player Turn 3 to 6 in contact with it.
\n\nWinning conditions: you complete this Secondary Objective if, at the end of the game, the marked Terrain Feature was not plundered.</string>

  <string name="secondaryobjective_06">Master the Veil</string>
  <string name="secondaryobjective_06_description_short">Setup during Pre-game Selections: Mark the centre of the Battlefield.</string>
  <string name="secondaryobjective_06_description">Rules: None.
\n\nWinning conditions: you complete this Secondary Objective if, at the end of the game, you have a Caster or a model with Channel, within 9′′ of the centre of Battlefield, and the opponent does not.</string>

  <string name="secondaryobjective_07">Seize and Secure</string>
  <string name="secondaryobjective_07_description_short">Setup during Pre-game Selections: the opponent marks a Terrain Feature on the Battlefield that is fully outside their Deployment Zone, and that is not a Wall nor Impassable Terrain.</string>
  <string name="secondaryobjective_07_description">Rules: the marked Terrain Feature is “plundered” if a friendly Scoring Unit starts any of its Player Turn 3 to 6 in contact with it.
\n\nWinning conditions: you complete this Secondary Objective if, at the end of the game, the marked Terrain Feature was plundered.</string>

  <string name="secondaryobjective_08">Settle the Score</string>
  <string name="secondaryobjective_08_description_short">Setup during Pre-game Selections: you mark a unit from the opponent’s Army List.</string>
  <string name="secondaryobjective_08_description">Rules: None.
\n\nWinning conditions: you complete this Secondary Objective if, at the end of the game, the marked unit is removed as a casualty, Decimated, or Shaken.</string>

  <string name="secondaryobjective_09">Slay the Beast</string>
  <string name="secondaryobjective_09_description_short">Setup during Pre-game Selections: the opponent marks the two most expensive non-Scoring Units from their Army List. If there is only one non-Scoring Unit, also mark the most expensive Scoring Unit. If there are no non-Scoring units, mark the two most expensive Scoring Units instead. In any case of tie, randomize.</string>
  <string name="secondaryobjective_09_description">Rules: None.
\n\nWinning conditions: you complete this Secondary Objective if, at the end of the game, at least one of the marked units is removed as a casualty, Decimated, Shaken, or in contact with its own Deployment Zone.</string>

  <string name="secondaryobjective_10">Stand Firm</string>
  <string name="secondaryobjective_10_description_short">Setup during Pre-game Selections: the opponent marks two Rank-and-File units from your Army List. If possible, each of these must be a Scoring Unit.</string>
  <string name="secondaryobjective_10_description">Rules: None.
\n\nWinning conditions: you complete this Secondary Objective if, at the end of the game, neither of the marked units are removed as a casualty, Decimated, or Shaken.</string>

  <string name="secondaryobjective_11">Unleash the Big Guns</string>
  <string name="secondaryobjective_11_description_short">Setup during Pre-game Selections: you mark two Terrain Features on the Battlefield that are not fully within your Deployment Zone, and that are not Walls nor Impassable Terrain. Then mark all non-Characters units from your Army List that have Shooting Weapons, and one Scoring Unit without Shooting Weapons. If less than five units have been marked, you may mark one additional Scoring Unit.</string>
  <string name="secondaryobjective_11_description">Rules: None.
\n\nWinning conditions: you complete this Secondary Objective if, at the end of the game, you have a non-Shaken marked unit in both nominated Terrain Features.</string>

  <string name="secondaryobjective_12">Work as One</string>
  <string name="secondaryobjective_12_description_short">Setup during Pre-game Selections: Mark the centre of the Battlefield.</string>
  <string name="secondaryobjective_12_description">Rules: None.
\n\nWinning conditions: you complete this Secondary Objective if, at the end of the game, you have more Scoring Units within 9′′ of the centre of Battlefield than the opponent has.</string>

  <string name="terrainlayout">Terrain Layout</string>
  <string name="terrainlayout_01">Clearwater Springs</string>
  <string name="terrainlayout_02">Ancient Fortifications</string>
  <string name="terrainlayout_03">Ancient Fortifications</string>
  <string name="terrainlayout_04">Abandoned Settlement</string>
  <string name="terrainlayout_05">Historic Battlefield</string>
  <string name="terrainlayout_06">Mountainous Crags</string>
  <string name="terrainlayout_preview">Terrain Layout Preview</string>

  <string name="listimport_import_from_clipboard">Load list from clipboard</string>
  <string name="listimport_import_instructions_1">Select preview of your army list in NEW RECRUIT format\nSelect all text\nSelect \"SHARE\"\nSelect \"9th Age Quick Setup\" from the applications list.</string>
  <string name="listimport_import_instructions_2">or</string>
  <string name="listimport_import_instructions_3">Select preview of your army list in NEW RECRUIT format\nSelect all text\nSelect \"COPY\"\nCome back to 9th Age Quick Setup app\nSelect the button below.</string>
  <string name="listimport_import_error">Could not import list based on text:</string>
</resources>