<resources>
  <string name="app_name">9th Age Quick Setup</string>
  <string name="bottom_navigation_quick_game_setup">Quick game setup</string>
  <string name="bottom_navigation_battle_outcome">Battle outcome</string>
  <string name="options_include_aleternative_maps">Alternative maps</string>
  <string name="generateNewConfiguration">Roll for new set</string>
  <string name="enlarge">Enlarge</string>
  <string name="details">Details</string>
  <string name="deployment">Deployment</string>
  <string name="ok">OK</string>
  <string name="preview_list">Preview list</string>
  <string name="points">%d\u200Apts</string>
  <string name="conflict_side_choose_hint">Army owner:</string>
  <string name="conflict_side_me">This is my army</string>
  <string name="conflict_side_opponent">This is my opponent\'s army</string>
  <string name="deployment_01">Frontline Clash</string>
  <string name="deployment_01_description">Deployment Zones are more than 12″ away from the Central Line, towards your Long Table Edge, and more than 6″ from the Short Table Edges.</string>
  <string name="deployment_02">Bottleneck</string>
  <string name="deployment_02_description">Player A’s Deployment Zone is more than 9″ away from the Central Line, towards your Long Table Edge, and more than 12″ from the Short Table Edges. Player B’s Deployment Zone is more than 15″ away from the Central Line. Whoever chooses its Deployment Zone also chooses if they are player A or player B.</string>
  <string name="deployment_03">Spearhead</string>
  <string name="deployment_03_description">Deployment Zones are more than 15″ away from the Central Line. The table is divided along the long Table Edge into 3 equal areas (west, centre, east). The player who chooses its Deployment Zone also chooses one of these thirds to be their Spearhead Area. The other player then chooses one of the remaining two thirds as their Spearhead Area. Units deployed fully within their Spearhead Area gain Vanguard (3″).</string>
  <string name="deployment_04"> Mutual Encroachment</string>
  <string name="deployment_04_description">Deployment Zones are more than 12″ away from the Central Line, towards your Long Table Edge, and more than 6″ from the Short Table Edges. When deploying, each player may Deploy up to two of their Core Scoring Units fully on their own half of the Battlefield and fully within any Field, Forest, or Ruins (i.e. no parts of the Unit Boundary outside the Terrain Feature or on the opponent’s half of the Battlefield). Units Deployed in this way cannot declare a Charge, perform Advance Move, or perform a March Move in the first Player Turn of the first Game Turn.</string>
  <string name="deployment_05">Refused Flank</string>
  <string name="deployment_05_description">Deployment Zones are more than 9″ away from the Central Line (see figure). The Central Line is the line drawn from one corner to the opposite corner. The player that chooses its Deployment Zone also chooses which corners to use for the Central Line</string>
  <string name="deployment_06">Cornerstone</string>
  <string name="deployment_06_description">Deployment Zones are more than 12″ away from the Central Line, towards your Long Table Edge, and more than 6″ from the Short Table Edges. The first unit each player deploys must be their most expensive Rank-and-File unit (on the Army List). This unit must be deployed within 6″ of the Central Line that is parallel to the Short Table Edges (dashed red line in the figure). When deployment is finished, each player must have deployed an as equal number of units as possible on each side of the first deployed unit. Which side a unit is deployed on is defined by which short table edge the unit’s centre is closer to (compared to the first deployed unit). Ignore Attachable Models that start the game joined to a unit for this.</string>
  <string name="deployment_preview">Deployment Preview</string>

  <string name="primaryobjective">Primary Objective</string>
  <string name="primaryobjective_01">Spoils of War</string>
  <string name="primaryobjective_01_description_short">Setup during Pre-game Selections: None.</string>
  <string name="primaryobjective_01_description">Rules: When an enemy Scoring Unit is Destroyed in Combat, the opposing player puts one Spoils Token on one of their Scoring Units (if there are any) that was just engaged with the unit Destroyed in Combat. A unit loses all its Spoils Tokens when any of the following occurs:
\n\n\t• The last Health Point on its Rank-and-File models (see Models and Units in the Definitions and Terminology
chapter) is lost.
\n\n\t• It becomes Shaken. Remember that units that perform a Flee Move automatically become Shaken.
\n\nWinning conditions: At the end of the game, the player with the most Spoils Token on their units wins this Primary Objective.</string>
  <string name="primaryobjective_02">Breakthrough</string>
  <string name="primaryobjective_02_description_short">Setup during Pre-game Selections: Mark Deployment Zones.</string>
  <string name="primaryobjective_02_description">Rules: None.
    \n\nWinning conditions: At the end of the game, each player adds together the number of Scoring Units in their opponent’s Deployment Zone and the number of enemy units that were Scoring at the start of the game that were Destroyed in Combat. The player with the highest total wins the Primary Objective.</string>
  <string name="primaryobjective_03">Secure Target</string>
  <string name="primaryobjective_03_description_short">Setup during Pre-game Selections: Place two markers with their centers on the line dividing the board into halves (the dashed line in the figures describing Deployment Types), one on each side of the centre of the table, as close as possible to a third of the length of the long Board Edge (24″ on a 72″ wide board) away from it, and more than 1″ away from Impassable Terrain.</string>
  <string name="primaryobjective_03_description">Rules: A marker is controlled if a player has at least one Scoring Unit within 6″ of the centre of the marker, and the other player does not.
    \n\nWinning conditions: At the end of Game Turns 3–6, a Victory Counter is awarded to a Player which controls an Objective. The player with the most such Victory Counters at the end of the game wins this Primary Objective.</string>
  <string name="primaryobjective_04">Forage and Plunder</string>
  <string name="primaryobjective_04_description_short">Setup during Pre-game Selections: Both players nominate a Terrain Feature that is fully outside their Deployment Zone , they may nominate the same. Impassable Terrain and Walls cannot be nominated.</string>
  <string name="primaryobjective_04_description">Rules: You automatically plunder a nominated Terrain Feature when one of your Scoring Units starts any of its Player Turn 3–6 in contact with it, each Terrain Feature can only be plundered once by each player.
    \n\nWinning conditions: At the end of the game, if one player has plundered more nominated Terrain Features than the other player they win this Primary Objective.</string>
  <string name="primaryobjective_05">Hold the Centre</string>
  <string name="primaryobjective_05_description_short">Setup during Pre-game Selections: Mark the centre of the table.</string>
  <string name="primaryobjective_05_description">Rules: The battlefield is controlled by the player with the most Scoring Units within 9″ of the centre of the table (if both players have an equal number of Scoring Units, no one controls it).
    \n\nWinning conditions: At the end of Game Turns 3–6, a Victory Counter is awarded to a Player who controls at least one marker. The player with the most such Victory Counters at the end of the game wins this Primary Objective.</string>
  <string name="primaryobjective_06">Hidden Agendas</string>
  <string name="primaryobjective_06_description_short">Setup during Pre-game Selections: None.</string>
  <string name="primaryobjective_06_description">Rules: None.
    \n\nWinning conditions: If one player is the sole winner of their Secondary Objective, this player is rewarded +4 Battle Points and the opponent loses 4 Battle Points. This replaces the normal Battle Points bonus for winning Primary and Secondary Objectives.</string>

  <string name="primaryobjective_05_legacy">Breaking flags</string>
  <string name="primaryobjective_05_description_short_legacy">Valuable targets must be annihilated.</string>
  <string name="primaryobjective_05_description_legacy">After Spell Selection (at the end of step 7 of the PreGame Sequence), mark all Scoring Units on both players’ Army Lists. If either player has fewer than 3 marked units, their opponent must mark enough units from this player’s Army List so that there are exactly 3 marked units in the army, starting with the player who chose their Deployment Zone.
    \n\nThe player who has the lowest number of their marked units removed as casualties at the end of the game wins this Secondary Objective.</string>
  <string name="primaryobjective_06_legacy">Secure Target</string>
  <string name="primaryobjective_06_description_short_legacy">Critical resources must not fall into enemy hands.</string>
  <string name="primaryobjective_06_description_legacy">Immediately after determining Deployment Zones, both players place one marker on the Battlefield, starting with the player who chose their Deployment Zone. Each player must place the marker with its centre on a point that is more than 12″ away from their Deployment Zone and at least a third of the long Board Edge length (24″ on a standard board) from the point marked by the other marker.
    \n\nAt the end of the game, the player controlling the most markers wins this Secondary Objective. A marker is controlled by the player with the most Scoring Units within 6″ of the centre of the marker. If a unit is within 6″ of the centres of both markers, it only counts as within 6″ of the centre of the marker which is closest to its Centre (randomise if both markers’ centres are equally close).</string>

  <string name="mysecondaryobjective">My Secondary Objective</string>
  <string name="opponentsecondaryobjective">Opponents Secondary Objective</string>

  <string name="secondaryobjective_01">Capture the Flag</string>
  <string name="secondaryobjective_01_description_short">Setup during Pre-game Selections: None.</string>
  <string name="secondaryobjective_01_description">Rules: None.
\n\nWinning conditions: At the end of the game, you win this Secondary Objective if you have more Standard Bearers and Battle Standard Bearers on the Battlefield, than the opponent has.</string>

  <string name="secondaryobjective_02">Commit to Battle</string>
  <string name="secondaryobjective_02_description_short">Setup during Pre-game Selections: None.</string>
  <string name="secondaryobjective_02_description">Rules: None.
\n\nWinning conditions: At the end of the game, you win this Secondary Objective if you have more Scoring Units in your opponent’s Deployment Zone than the opponent has (in their own Deployment Zone).</string>

  <string name="secondaryobjective_03">Demonstrate Superiority</string>
  <string name="secondaryobjective_03_description_short">Setup during Pre-game Selections: The opponent nominates the two most expensive Scoring Units from their Army List. In case of a tie, randomize. If there are no Scoring Units, nominate the most expensive Rank-and-File unit instead.</string>
  <string name="secondaryobjective_03_description">Rules: None.
\n\nWinning conditions: At the end of the game, you win this Secondary Objective if at least one of the nominated units Destroyed, Decimated, Shaken, or if it is touching its own Deployment Zone.</string>

  <string name="secondaryobjective_04">Enslave and Ransom</string>
  <string name="secondaryobjective_04_description_short">Setup during Pre-game Selections: None.</string>
  <string name="secondaryobjective_04_description">Rules: An enemy unit is enslaved whenever it is destroyed during a Round of Combat in step 5 of the Round of Combat sequence (Breaking and Pursuing). This includes failing a Break Test and being caught or dying during the Flee Move, Supernal unit failing a Break Test or Unstable unit losing a Combat and being wiped due to HP loss. This does not include units being destroyed as a direct result of Melee Attacks. Ignore Attachable Models joined to units with Rank-and-File models.
\n\nWinning conditions: You win this Secondary Objective if at least two enemy units have been enslaved during the course of the game.</string>

  <string name="secondaryobjective_05">Forbid Trespass</string>
  <string name="secondaryobjective_05_description_short">Setup during Pre-game Selections: You nominate a Terrain Feature on the Battlefield that is fully outside your Deployment Zone. Impassable Terrain and Walls cannot be nominated.</string>
  <string name="secondaryobjective_05_description">Rules: A nominated Terrain Feature is plundered when an enemy Scoring Unit starts any of its Player Turn 3–6 in contact with it.
\n\nWinning conditions: At the end of the game, you win this Secondary Objective if the nominated Terrain Feature was not plundered.</string>

  <string name="secondaryobjective_06">Master the Veil</string>
  <string name="secondaryobjective_06_description_short">Setup during Pre-game Selections: Mark the centre of the table.</string>
  <string name="secondaryobjective_06_description">Rules: None.
\n\nWinning conditions: At the end of the game, you win this Secondary Objective if you have a model with Channel, or that knows a spell (Learned Spell or Bound Spell), within 9″ of the centre of table, and the opponent has not.</string>

  <string name="secondaryobjective_07">Seize and Secure</string>
  <string name="secondaryobjective_07_description_short">Setup during Pre-game Selections: The opponent nominates a Terrain Feature on the Battlefield that is fully outside their Deployment Zone. Impassable Terrain and Walls cannot be nominated.</string>
  <string name="secondaryobjective_07_description">Rules: A nominated Terrain Feature is plundered when a friendly Scoring Unit starts any of its Player Turn 3–6 in contact with it.
\n\nWinning conditions: At the end of the game, you win this Secondary Objective if the nominated Terrain Feature was plundered.</string>

  <string name="secondaryobjective_08">Settle the Score</string>
  <string name="secondaryobjective_08_description_short">Setup during Pre-game Selections: You nominate a unit from the opponent’s Army List.</string>
  <string name="secondaryobjective_08_description">Rules: None.
\n\nWinning conditions: At the end of the game, you win this Secondary Objective, if the nominated unit Destroyed, Decimated, or Shaken.</string>

  <string name="secondaryobjective_09">Slay the Beast</string>
  <string name="secondaryobjective_09_description_short">Setup during Pre-game Selections: The opponent nominates the two most expensive non-Scoring Units from their Army List. In case of a tie, randomize. If there are not enough non-Scoring Units, nominate the most expensive Scoring Units instead.</string>
  <string name="secondaryobjective_09_description">Rules: None.
\n\nWinning conditions: At the end of the game, you win this Secondary Objective, if at least one of the nominated units is has been Destroyed, Decimated, Shaken, or if it is touching its own Deployment Zone.</string>

  <string name="secondaryobjective_10">Stand Firm</string>
  <string name="secondaryobjective_10_description_short">Setup during Pre-game Selections: The opponent nominates two Scoring units from your Army List. If there are no Scoring Units, instead they nominate Rank-and-File units.</string>
  <string name="secondaryobjective_10_description">Rules: None.
\n\nWinning conditions: At the end of the game, you win this Secondary Objective if neither of the nominated units are Destroyed, Decimated, or Shaken.</string>

  <string name="secondaryobjective_11">Unleash the Big Guns</string>
  <string name="secondaryobjective_11_description_short">Setup during Pre-game Selections: You nominate two Terrain Features on the Battlefield that are not fully within your Deployment Zone. Impassable Terrain and Walls cannot be nominated. Then mark up to two units, the most expensive Scoring units from your Army List. In case of a tie, randomize.</string>
  <string name="secondaryobjective_11_description">Rules: None.
\n\nWinning conditions: At the end of the game, you win this Secondary Objective if you have a model with a Shooting Weapon or a marked Scoring Unit, in both nominated Terrain Features. One unit cannot be counted against both Terrain Features. Characters do not count.</string>

  <string name="secondaryobjective_12">Work as One</string>
  <string name="secondaryobjective_12_description_short">Setup during Pre-game Selections: Mark the centre of the table.</string>
  <string name="secondaryobjective_12_description">Rules: None.
\n\nWinning conditions: At the end of the game, you win this Secondary Objective if you have at least two Scoring Units within 9″ of the centre of table, and the opponent does not have two or more.</string>

  <string name="terrainlayout">Terrain Layout</string>
  <string name="terrainlayout_01">Shrouded Pool</string>
  <string name="terrainlayout_02">Foothill Outpost</string>
  <string name="terrainlayout_03">Dilapidated Manor</string>
  <string name="terrainlayout_04">Volcanic Lake</string>
  <string name="terrainlayout_05">Misty Marshes</string>
  <string name="terrainlayout_06">Ancient Walls</string>
  <string name="terrainlayout_07">Beacon Hill</string>
  <string name="terrainlayout_08">Witch\'s Cottage</string>
  <string name="terrainlayout_09">Mage\'s Sanctum</string>
  <string name="terrainlayout_10">Villa Grounds</string>
  <string name="terrainlayout_11">Ancient Fortress</string>
  <string name="terrainlayout_12">Frontier Farm</string>
  <string name="terrainlayout_13">Ravaged Watchtower</string>
  <string name="terrainlayout_14">Creeping Forest</string>
  <string name="terrainlayout_15">Eerie Graveyard</string>
  <string name="terrainlayout_16">Shattered Bridge</string>
  <string name="terrainlayout_preview">Terrain Layout Preview</string>

  <string name="listimport_import_from_clipboard">Load list from clipboard</string>
  <string name="listimport_import_instructions_1">Select preview of your army list in NEW RECRUIT format\nSelect all text\nSelect \"SHARE\"\nSelect \"9th Age Quick Setup\" from the applications list.</string>
  <string name="listimport_import_instructions_2">or</string>
  <string name="listimport_import_instructions_3">Select preview of your army list in NEW RECRUIT format\nSelect all text\nSelect \"COPY\"\nCome back to 9th Age Quick Setup app\nSelect the button below.</string>
  <string name="listimport_import_error">Could not import list based on text:</string>
</resources>