<resources>
  <string name="app_name">Quick Setup</string>
  <string name="generateNewConfiguration">Roll for new set</string>
  <string name="enlarge">Enlarge</string>
  <string name="details">Details</string>
  <string name="deployment">Deployment</string>
  <string name="deployment_01">Frontline Clash</string>
  <string name="deployment_01_description">Deployment Zones are areas more than 12″ away from the Centre Line</string>
  <string name="deployment_02">Dawn Assault</string>
  <string name="deployment_02_description">The player choosing the Deployment Zone also chooses a short Board Edge and the other player gets the opposite short Board Edge. Deployment Zones are areas more than 12″ away from the Centre Line and more than &#188; of the board’s length from the opponent’s short Board Edge (18″ on a 72″ board). When declaring Special Deployment, players may choose to keep up to two of their units as reinforcement. These units follow the rules for Ambushing units, except that they must be placed touching the owner’s short Board Edge when they arrive.</string>
  <string name="deployment_03">Counterthrust</string>
  <string name="deployment_03_description">Deployment Zones are areas more than 8″ away from the Centre Line. Units must be deployed more than 20″ away from enemy units. During their first 3 deployment turns, each player must deploy a single unit if possible, and cannot deploy any Characters unless they have to. Units using Special Deployment, such as Scout, ignore these restrictions and follow their Special Deployment rules.</string>
  <string name="deployment_04">Encircle</string>
  <string name="deployment_04_description">The player choosing the Deployment Zone decides if they want to be the attacker or the defender. The attacker must deploy more than 9″ from the Centre Line if entirely within a quarter of the board’s length from either short Board Edge (18″ on a 72″ board), and more than 15″from the Centre Line elsewhere. The defender does the opposite: more than 15″ away from the Centre Line if within a quarter of the board’s length from the short Board Edge, and more than 9″ away from the Centre Line elsewhere.</string>
  <string name="deployment_05">Refused Flank</string>
  <string name="deployment_05_description">The board is divided into halves by a diagonal line across the board. Whoever gets to choose the Deployment Zone decides which diagonal to use. Deployment Zones are areas more than 9″ away from this line.</string>
  <string name="deployment_06">Marching Columns</string>
  <string name="deployment_06_description">Deployment Zones are areas more than 12″ away from the Centre Line.\n\nEach player must choose a short Board Edge when deploying their first unit. Each unit this player deploys
afterwards must be deployed with its Centre farther away from the chosen short Board Edge than the Centre of the last unit this player deployed (measure from the closest point on the short Board Edge). Characters, War Machines, War Platforms, and Scouting units
ignore these rules.\n\nDuring their first 3 deployment turns, each player must deploy a single unit if possible, and cannot deploy any Characters, War Machines, or War Platforms unless they have to.\n\nInstead of deploying a unit, a player may choose to make all
their undeployed units Delayed that are not using Special Deployment. Delayed units follow the rules for Ambushing units with the following exceptions:\n\n
• In each Player Turn, after rolling for all Ambushing units, the Reactive Player chooses the order in which all Delayed units that passed the 3+ roll enter the Battlefield.\n\n
• In the chosen order, each unit must be placed one after the other with the centre of its rear rank as close as possible to the centre of the long Board Edge in their owner’s Deployment Zone, before any nonDelayed Ambushers are placed on the Battlefield.\n\n
• After all arriving units have been placed, they can be moved as described in the rules for Ambush (see page 80).</string>
  <string name="deployment_preview">Deployment Preview</string>

  <string name="secondaryobjective">Secondary Objective</string>
  <string name="secondaryobjective_01">Hold the Ground</string>
  <string name="secondaryobjective_01_description_short">Secure and hold the centre of the Battlefield.</string>
  <string name="secondaryobjective_01_description">Mark the centre of the board. At the end of each Game Turn after the first, the player with the most Scoring Units within 6″ of the centre of the board gains a counter. At the end of the game, the player with the most such counters wins this Secondary Objective.</string>
  <string name="secondaryobjective_02">Breakthrough</string>
  <string name="secondaryobjective_02_description_short">Invade the enemy territory.</string>
  <string name="secondaryobjective_02_description">The player with the most Scoring Units inside their opponent’s Deployment Zone at the end of the game, up to a maximum of 3, wins this Secondary Objective.</string>
  <string name="secondaryobjective_03">Spoils of War</string>
  <string name="secondaryobjective_03_description_short">Gather precious loot.</string>
  <string name="secondaryobjective_03_description">Place 3 markers along the line dividing the board into halves (the dashed line in the figures describing Deployment Types). One marker is placed with its centre on a point on this line that is as close as possible to the centre of the board while still being more than 1″ away from Impassable Terrain. The other two markers are placed with their centres on points on this line that are on either side of the central marker, as close to the centre of the board as possible but at least a third of the length of the long Board Edge (24″ on a standard board) away from it, and more than 1″ away from Impassable Terrain.
    \n\nAt the start of each of your Player Turns, each of your Scoring units that is not carrying a marker may pick up a single marker whose centre they are in contact with. Remove the marker from the Battlefield: the unit is now carrying the marker. Units carrying a marker with fewer than 3 Full Ranks cannot perform March Moves.\n\n
    \n\nIf a unit carrying a marker is destroyed or loses Scoring, the opponent must immediately place the marker carried by this unit with its centre on a point within 3″ of it. Ignore Post-Combat Reform for this purpose. This point cannot be within 1″ of Impassable Terrain, but it can be inside a unit.
    \n\nAt the end of the game, the player with the most units carrying markers wins this Secondary Objective.</string>
  <string name="secondaryobjective_04">King of the Hill</string>
  <string name="secondaryobjective_04_description_short">Desecrate your opponent’s holy ground while protecting yours.</string>
  <string name="secondaryobjective_04_description">After Spell Selection (at the end of step 7 of the PreGame Sequence), both players choose a Terrain Feature that isn’t Impassable Terrain and that is not fully inside their Deployment Zone, starting with the player who chose their Deployment Zone (note that both players may choose the same Terrain Feature).
    \n\nA player captures their opponent’s chosen Terrain Feature if any of the player’s Scoring Units are inside that Terrain Feature at the end of the game. If a player captures their opponent’s chosen Terrain Feature while not allowing their own to be captured, they win this Secondary Objective.</string>
  <string name="secondaryobjective_05">Capture the Flags</string>
  <string name="secondaryobjective_05_description_short">Valuable targets must be annihilated.</string>
  <string name="secondaryobjective_05_description">After Spell Selection (at the end of step 7 of the PreGame Sequence), mark all Scoring Units on both players’ Army Lists. If either player has fewer than 3 marked units, their opponent must mark enough units from this player’s Army List so that there are exactly 3 marked units in the army, starting with the player who chose their Deployment Zone.
    \n\nThe player who has the lowest number of their marked units removed as casualties at the end of the game wins this Secondary Objective.</string>
  <string name="secondaryobjective_06">Secure Target</string>
  <string name="secondaryobjective_06_description_short">Critical resources must not fall into enemy hands.</string>
  <string name="secondaryobjective_06_description">Immediately after determining Deployment Zones, both players place one marker on the Battlefield, starting with the player who chose their Deployment Zone. Each player must place the marker with its centre on a point that is more than 12″ away from their Deployment Zone and at least a third of the long Board Edge length (24″ on a standard board) from the point marked by the other marker.
    \n\nAt the end of the game, the player controlling the most markers wins this Secondary Objective. A marker is controlled by the player with the most Scoring Units within 6″ of the centre of the marker. If a unit is within 6″ of the centres of both markers, it only counts as within 6″ of the centre of the marker which is closest to its Centre (randomise if both markers’ centres are equally close).</string>


  <string name="terrainlayout">Terrain Layout</string>
  <string name="terrainlayout_01">Shrouded Pool</string>
  <string name="terrainlayout_02">Foothill Outpost</string>
  <string name="terrainlayout_03">Dilapidated Manor</string>
  <string name="terrainlayout_04">Volcanic Lake</string>
  <string name="terrainlayout_05">Misty Marshes</string>
  <string name="terrainlayout_06">Ancient Walls</string>
  <string name="terrainlayout_07">Beacon Hill</string>
  <string name="terrainlayout_08">Witch\'s Cottage</string>
  <string name="terrainlayout_09">Mage\'s Sanctum</string>
  <string name="terrainlayout_10">Villa Grounds</string>
  <string name="terrainlayout_11">Ancient Fortress</string>
  <string name="terrainlayout_12">Frontier Farm</string>
  <string name="terrainlayout_13">Ravaged Watchtower</string>
  <string name="terrainlayout_14">Creeping Forest</string>
  <string name="terrainlayout_15">Eerie Graveyard</string>
  <string name="terrainlayout_16">Shattered Bridge</string>
  <string name="terrainlayout_preview">Terrain Layout Preview</string>
</resources>