<resources>
  <string name="app_name">9th Age Quick Setup</string>
  <string name="bottom_navigation_quick_game_setup">Quick game setup</string>
  <string name="bottom_navigation_battle_outcome">Battle outcome</string>
  <string name="options_include_aleternative_maps">Alternative maps</string>
  <string name="generateNewConfiguration">Roll for new set</string>
  <string name="enlarge">Enlarge</string>
  <string name="details">Details</string>
  <string name="deployment">Deployment</string>
  <string name="ok">OK</string>
  <string name="preview_list">Preview list</string>
  <string name="points">%d\u200Apts</string>
  <string name="conflict_side_choose_hint">Army owner:</string>
  <string name="conflict_side_me">This is my army</string>
  <string name="conflict_side_opponent">This is my opponent\'s army</string>
  <string name="deployment_01">Frontline Clash</string>
  <string name="deployment_01_description">Deployment Zones are more than 12″ away from the Central Line, and more than 6″ from the Short Battlefield Edges.</string>
  <string name="deployment_02">Bottleneck</string>
  <string name="deployment_02_description">Player A’s Deployment Zone is more than 9″ away from the Cent- ral Line, and more than 12″ from the Short Battlefield Edges. Player B’s Deployment Zone is more than 15″ away from the Central Line. The Defender also chooses if they are player A or player B.</string>
  <string name="deployment_03">Spearhead</string>
  <string name="deployment_03_description">Deployment Zones are more than 15″ away from the Central Line. The table is divided along the Long Battlefield Edge into three equal areas (‘west’, ‘centre’, ‘east’). The Defender also chooses one of these thirds to be their ‘Spearhead Area’. The Attacker then immediately chooses one of the remaining two thirds as their Spearhead Area. units Deployed entirely within their Spearhead Area gain Vanguard (3″).</string>
  <string name="deployment_04">Encircle</string>
  <string name="deployment_04_description">Each Deployment Zone alternates between 9″ and 15″ from the Central Line, as shown in the diagram. Along with selecting a side, the Defender selects one of the two De- ployment Zones. The Attacker has the other Deployment Zone.</string>
  <string name="deployment_05">Refused Flank</string>
  <string name="deployment_05_description">Deployment Zones are more than 9″ away from the Central Line (see diagram), which is the line drawn from one corner of the Battlefield to the opposite corner. The Defender chooses which corners to use.</string>
  <string name="deployment_06">Assault at First Light</string>
  <string name="deployment_06_description">After choosing a side the Defender selects a Short Battlefield Edge; the Attacker has the opposite one. Defenders Deployment Zone is more than 6″ away from the Central Line, and 18″ away from the Attackers Short Battlefield Edge. Attackers Deployment Zone is instead more than 12″ away from the Central Line, and 18″ away from the Defenders Short Battlefield Edge.</string>
  <string name="deployment_preview">Deployment Preview</string>

  <string name="primaryobjective">Primary Objective</string>
  <string name="primaryobjective_01">Trophies of War</string>
  <string name="primaryobjective_01_description_short">Setup during Pre-game Selections: None.</string>
  <string name="primaryobjective_01_description"> Rules: whenever an Enemy unit Engaged in Combat,including all Attached Models, is removed as a casualty, put a single Trophy Token on a single Friendly Scoring unit that was just Engaged with the removed unit. A unit immediately loses all its Trophy Tokens if it loses Scoring.
    \n\nEnd of Game Completion: the player with the most Trophy Tokens on their units wins.
    \n\nIf both players have no Tokens and one player also has no Scoring units, remaining on the Battlefield, the other player wins.</string>
  <string name="primaryobjective_02">Divide and Conquer</string>
  <string name="primaryobjective_02_description_short">Setup during Pre-game Selections: mark the Battlefield Centre and divide the Battlefield into quarters.</string>
  <string name="primaryobjective_02_description">Rules: END of Game Turns 3 to 6, a player gains a single Objective Counter if they have more quarters touching Friendly Scoring units than the opponent has. Each unit can only touch a single quarter at a time, determined by the location of its Centre.
  \nA unit with its Centre within 9″ of the Battlefield Centre does not count as being in Contact with any quarter.
  \n\nEnd of Game Completion: the player with the most Objective Counters wins.
  </string>  <string name="primaryobjective_03">Breakthrough</string>
  <string name="primaryobjective_03_description_short">Setup during Pre-game Selections: mark all Scoring units on the opponent’s Army List</string>
  <string name="primaryobjective_03_description">
    Rules: none.
    \n\nEnd of Game Completion: combine the number of:
    \n1. marked Enemy units that were removed as a casualty whilst Engaged in Combat and
    \n2. Friendly Scoring units in Contact with the Enemy’s Deployment Zone.
  </string>
  <string name="primaryobjective_04">Secure Target</string>
  <string name="primaryobjective_04_description_short">Setup during Pre-game Selections: place two markers on opposite sides of the Battlefield, with their centres on the Central Line and 18″* from the Battlefield Centre.</string>
  <string name="primaryobjective_04_description">
    Rules: END of Game Turns 3 to 6, a player gains a single Objective Counter if they control more markers than their opponent. A marker is controlled if there are any Friendly Scoring units and no Enemy Scoring units within 6″ of a marker.
    \n\nEnd of Game Completion: the player with the most Objective Counters wins.
    \n\n* For Battlefields of a larger or smaller size than the standard 72″×48″, replace 18″ with a distance equal to a quarter of the Long Battlefield Edge.
    </string>
  <string name="primaryobjective_05">Hold the Centre</string>
  <string name="primaryobjective_05_description_short">Setup during Pre-game Selections: mark the Battlefield Centre.</string>
  <string name="primaryobjective_05_description">
    Rules: END of Game Turns 3 to 6, the player with the most Scoring units within 9″ of the Battlefield Centre gains a single Objective Counter.
    \n\nEnd of Game Completion: the player with the most Objective Counters wins.
  </string>
  <string name="primaryobjective_06">Skull of Harald Redstub</string>
  <string name="primaryobjective_06_description_short">Setup during Pre-game Selections: place a marker on the Battlefield Centre and two markers on opposite sides of the Battlefield, with their centres on the Central Line and 18″* from the Battlefield Centre. Then place a single Clue Token on each Terrain Feature except Impassable Terrain and playermade Terrain Features.</string>
  <string name="primaryobjective_06_description">
  Rules: START of each Friendly Player Turn, pick up a Clue Token from each Terrain Feature where:
  \n• there is a Clue Token,
  \n• a Friendly Scoring unit is in Contact, and
  \n• no Enemy Scoring units are in Contact.
  \n\nEND of Game Turn 3, the player with the most Clue Token selects which marker holds the Skull. In case of a tie, the marker at the Battlefield Centre is selected.
  \n\nEnd of Game Completion: the player with the most Scoring units within 6″ of the Skull wins.
  \n\n* For Battlefields of a larger or smaller size the standard 72″x 48″, replace 18″ with a distance equal to a quarter of the Long Battlefield Edge.
  </string>
  <string name="secondaryobjectives_section_title">Secondary Objectives</string>
  <string name="secondaryobjectives_comment">
    If an Army List does not contain enough units that fulfil the requirements of a Secondary Objective, the relevant player first selects all units that fulfil the criteria and can then choose any units for the remaining choices.
    \n\nDuring Pre-game Selections, Defender picks one of the following objectives, the Attacker then immediately picks one of the remaining two.
  </string>

  <string name="secondaryobjectives_1">Secondary objective #1</string>
  <string name="secondaryobjectives_2">Secondary objective #2</string>
  <string name="secondaryobjectives_3">Secondary objective #3</string>

  <string name="secondaryobjective_01">Settle the Score</string>
  <string name="secondaryobjective_01_description_short">Pre-game Selections: on the opponent’s Army List mark TWO Rank-and-File units.</string>
  <string name="secondaryobjective_01_description">End of Game Completion: BOTH marked units are removed as a casualty, Decimated, or Shaken.</string>

  <string name="secondaryobjective_02">Demonstrate Superiority</string>
  <string name="secondaryobjective_02_description_short">Pre-game Selections: on the opponent’s Army List mark TWO Scoring units.</string>
  <string name="secondaryobjective_02_description">End of Game Completion: at least one of the marked units is removed as a casualty, Decimated, or Shaken.</string>

  <string name="secondaryobjective_03">Slay the Beast</string>
  <string name="secondaryobjective_03_description_short">Setup during Pre-game Selections: on the opponent’s Army List mark the TWO most expensive</string>
  <string name="secondaryobjective_03_description">Non-Scoring Rank-and-File units or Characters of Height 4&#8211;5 with Solitary. End of Game Completion: at least one of the marked units is removed as a casualty, Decimated, or Shaken</string>

  <string name="secondaryobjective_04">Assassinate</string>
  <string name="secondaryobjective_04_description_short">Setup during Pre-game Selections: on the opponent’s Army List mark TWO Characters. These must be: Characters who can be Deployed during Battle Setup. (Note: you cannot mark Hidden Characters.)</string>
  <string name="secondaryobjective_04_description">End of Game Completion: at least one of the marked units is removed as a casualty, Decimated, or Shaken.</string>

  <string name="secondaryobjective_05">Capture their Banners</string>
  <string name="secondaryobjective_05_description_short">Setup during Pre-game Selections: on the opponent’s Army List mark ALL Scoring units and The Battle Standard Bearer.
    \n\nAt least 3 units must be marked.</string>
  <string name="secondaryobjective_05_description">End of Game Completion: Three or more of the marked units are removed as a casualty, Decimated, or Shaken.</string>

  <string name="secondaryobjective_06">Conserve our Numbers</string>
  <string name="secondaryobjective_06_description_short">Setup during Pre-game Selections: on YOUR Army List the opponent marks ALL Scoring units and The Battle Standard Bearer.
    \n\nAt least 3 units must be marked.</string>
  <string name="secondaryobjective_06_description">End of Game Completion: three or more of the marked units are NEITHER removed as a casualty, nor Decimated, nor Shaken.</string>

  <string name="terrainlayout">Terrain Layout</string>
  <string name="terrainlayout_01">Clearwater Springs</string>
  <string name="terrainlayout_02">Ancient Fortifications</string>
  <string name="terrainlayout_03">Ancient Fortifications</string>
  <string name="terrainlayout_04">Abandoned Settlement</string>
  <string name="terrainlayout_05">Historic Battlefield</string>
  <string name="terrainlayout_06">Mountainous Crags</string>
  <string name="terrainlayout_preview">Terrain Layout Preview</string>

  <string name="listimport_import_from_clipboard">Load list from clipboard</string>
  <string name="listimport_import_instructions_1">Select preview of your army list in NEW RECRUIT format\nSelect all text\nSelect \"SHARE\"\nSelect \"9th Age Quick Setup\" from the applications list.</string>
  <string name="listimport_import_instructions_2">or</string>
  <string name="listimport_import_instructions_3">Select preview of your army list in NEW RECRUIT format\nSelect all text\nSelect \"COPY\"\nCome back to 9th Age Quick Setup app\nSelect the button below.</string>
  <string name="listimport_import_error">Could not import list based on text:</string>
</resources>